this is the time known as the great pirate era a countless array of pirates go to battle across
the seas in search of the one piece the legendary treasure left behind by gold roger king of the
pirates monkey d luffy a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum gum fruit set sail
to become the next king of the pirates as luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles they
capture the unwanted attention of the world government which will use any means necessary
to stop them on this site can't wait to see what kind of adventures up next with a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue the crew will cover path across the grand line to the new world
in an attempt to rescue his brother ace luffy enlisted the aid of the pirate empress boa hancock
to sneak onto a navy vessel on course to the government prison impelled down meanwhile the
other straw hats scattered around the globe by bartholomew kuma face struggles of their own
tequila wolf is a nation of laborers
the people we have constantly toiling away to build this bridge are criminals from all over the world
either that or they're citizens of countries that refuse to ally with the world government
in short they're slaves how much longer until the bridge is complete i have no idea now that you're
here we're putting you to work so the only thing you need to worry about is making the bridge
is this thing edible i've never seen this kind of fruit before
what the was that thing a plant and did it really just try to eat me sure they are man-eating plants
what the hell is this lake this is the swindling forest glimston
help help help
the red whereabouts the negative princess and the king of demons
It's way better.
Love, love, babe.
I can't do it.
I can't stop thinking about those women on Luffy's crew.
So, you're choosing those two girls over me, is that it?
You can't tie me down.
I'm a bad boy, Missy.
You're better off without me.
Just tell me what it is you don't like about me.
I promise I'll change for you.
Wait, don't leave me.
I won't give up, no matter what.
Because...
Even if there are two of them, my love for Luffy burns like the sun.
Can't eat another bite. That was so good.
Quiet!
Don't forget, you're a stowaway.
If you don't keep it down, you'll be found.
I never expected such a beautiful woman to burp and laugh like that.
Strangely enough, I find it sort of a turn on.
But something's still fishy.
Further investigation will be needed on this issue.
Elsewhere, Luffy's crew, who had been scattered by Kuma, found themselves facing more pressing matters.
Nope, still angry.
Still angry.
I'm still mad about this.
Look, I know what I said.
If I were to travel anywhere in the world, I would want to go someplace dark and damp with a creepy old castle.
And I would spend all my days singing songs of curses.
But...
Stupid Kuma!
I didn't know the castle wouldn't have any maids!
No servants! Nothing cute!
No bagel sandwiches and hot chocolate served to me in bed every morning!
And to top it off, there isn't a single stuffed animal here!
Here!
Where in the heck am I?
Oh, Moria!
Oh, Kumasi!
I miss you!
I want to go back to thriller park and...
What was that?
Yes, I knew it!
Someone else was exiled here just like me!
Oh, I hope it's someone cute!
Though I really shouldn't expect too much.
Either way, goodbye crushing loneliness!
No, is that...
It is!
It's one of the Straw Hats!
Kuma must have beaten him and launched him here.
Also, he looks pretty dead.
He's got all those bruises and stuff and he's still alive?!
Hmph!
It's only a matter of time, I guess.
He'll be dead soon enough.
Serves you right!
Hora! Hora! Hora! Hora! Hora! Hora!
Hora! Hora! Hora!
Hora, Hora! Hora!
Hora, Hora!
Hora! Hora! Hora!
Um.
I'm alive.
But where am I?
Hey, I knew you.
Retreat!
Negative holo!
I should just crawl around on the ground like a worm and eat dirt.
Where am I and why are you here?
I could ask you the same thing.
Also, don't scream like that.
What did you do with my swords?
Oh, you won't be getting those back.
I'm warning you.
This ought to slow you down.
Negative holo!
I'm nothing but garbage.
Someone should throw me away.
You're not so tough.
Or rather, I'm just super awesome.
How dare you!
Don't you growl at me like that.
It's not cute at all.
From now on, you're going to be my servant.
Understand me?
Now, no more talking.
Just be cute.
What the hell?
Stop that!
This is not okay!
No touching!
I won't be lonely ever again.
Crap!
I can't even move!
What the?
This is gross!
It's so messy!
You freak!
What did you do to me?
Get off!
I'm sorry I yelled at you.
Lesson learned.
You're forgiven.
You what?
I do apologize.
Wait, screw you!
I'll call you mistress.
I'll die tell.
I'll...
Okay, seriously.
Really sorry here.
All right, I get it!
That's enough!
I've wasted too much time here already.
I've got to go back.
Hey, dummy.
Exit's that way.
Huh?
Oh, gotcha.
No, wait!
I shouldn't have told him that!
Where are you going?
You're not even walking in the direction I pointed.
Hey!
Yeah, what is it?
Unless you tell me where you hid my swords,
I don't care.
Are you leaving now or what?
It's none of your damn business, piss off.
You won't get away from me that easily.
Huh?
Because you see, I've been lonely far too long.
I'm coming in the direction of Anand.
Huh?
Ahh!
Ah!
We call upon you, our great lord.
We pray to you, oh powerful one, to raid terror on our hateful enemies.
It is in your name that we make this wish.
We call upon you, lord of darkness.
We call upon you to answer us.
Come, Satan.
Grant the wish of those who praise you.
Praise Satan.
Oh.
Wow.
Ah!
Is... is this the devil?
Look, our magic incantation actually worked.
What a dreadful looking creature.
No kidding. It's not of this world.
This is what we've waited for. Our prayers are answered.
We'll have our revenge at last.
We don't have anything left. The Longarm Tribe took everything.
The bastards laid claim to everything we hold dear.
Oh great and powerful Satan, please grant us our wish.
In exchange, we are prepared to offer our souls up to you.
Leave them bloody and begging for death!
Praise Satan, King of the Devils! Praise Satan, King of the Devils!
Praise Satan, King of the Devils!
What is this place?
How far have I been carried away from all of my two friends?
More importantly, what in the world has happened to them?
Whatever their plight, I must aid them.
I'll return to meet the others at once.
Wait just a moment, please!
Don't go back to hell yet, Master Satan!
Quickly men, we've got to stop him!
We need to offer him more.
But what could we possibly offer Master Satan?
A sacrifice? Some blood?
What should we do?
I'll give up anything!
Anything to have our wish come true!
What do I want?
Come on!
Pardon me.
would you be so kind as to show me your panties he wants to see underwear everyone show him your
underwear um i i don't need to see any man panties thank you i uh and now we return to the present
where luffy is steadily speeding over the waves to the great prison impel down to rescue his brother
ace something stinks and i'm getting to the bottom of it
can't eat another bite that was so good quiet don't forget you're a stowaway if you don't keep it
down you'll be found excuse me is someone else in your room with you oh damn it lieutenant stalker
are you certain about this yes sir i just heard someone say oh i couldn't eat another bite and i
hardly think that the empress would say that to you he's right she'd never say that and if she did
i'll give myself a mohawk same here um i couldn't eat another bite
there i'm finished for now take these plates away oh yes and don't forget i require the same amount
five times every day that's a lot but if we give you that much how are we supposed to eat frankly i
don't care if you all starve to death that's awful but whatever she's hot there are now only six days
left until the public execution of portgus the ace with their guard ships destroyed at the hands of
whitebeard tensions at navy headquarters are rising famous marines from all over the world are
gathering at the harbor of marine ford prepared to battle to the death if need be
in the name of justice they ready their swords not for any mere battle but for war
meanwhile in the holy land of marijwa
the seven warlords is summoned for a meeting to determine their roles in the event that whitebeard
attacks ruffians that they are however they have little taste for the discussion
the mood in the room is tense and all hopes for teamwork or any sort of organization are quickly put to rest
as well
old man
huh how can you still be alive with all of those horrific wounds
nice
Because of you, Navy Headquarters is...
No, all of the world government is a mess.
Just kill me.
Do it. Kill me now.
So you want to die, huh?
You damned fool.
Nothing can be done now. Everything's in motion.
Even if you were to die right now, that won't stop Whitebeard from fighting.
There's nothing that can stop that anymore, son.
Seems the Navy has made the king of the sea.
Mad as hell.
No.
So...
Father.
Making it in, let alone making it out with an escaped prisoner.
On the next, One Piece!
A deadly infiltration!
The underwater prison impel down!
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!